Lesley Dreyer

full stack developer

ABOUT

I am a full stack developer with graphic design experience. I have been building projects in my free time using mostly JavaScript, React, Redux and Node.js. But I have taken classes in other languages in the past and am always up for learning new technologies! I would love to join a team where I can contribute and grow as a developer full time.

CODING PROJECTS

LUNCH AND A LAUGH

CODE: github.com/lesleydreyer/LunchAndALaugh DEMO: lesleydreyer.github.io/LunchAndALaugh

This application allows users to search for a restaurant through the Foursquare API and also provides a joke from a jokes API. I built this using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, & jQuery.

LET'S ROLL

CODE: github.com/lesleydreyer/letsroll

DEMO: <u>letsroll.herokuapp.com</u> (name: user1 password: user1234) This is a full stack and full CRUD application that allows users to schedule board game sessions with others. This project was built using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, Mocha, Chai, TravisCI & Heroku.

TRAIL TIME

CODE: github.com/lesleydreyer/trailtime

DEMO: trailtime.herokuapp.com (name: user1, password: user1234)

This is a full stack and full CRUD application that allows users to view off road trails and also add trails to the list. This project was built using HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, Mocha, Chai, Enzyme, Jest, TravisCI & Heroku.

WHAT THE SPUD

CODE: github.com/lesleydreyer/what-the-spud DEMO: whatthespud-d726f.firebaseapp.com

This is an application that is still in progress. It allows allows users to view and add recipes for potato dishes. This project is being built using HTML, CSS, React and Firebase.

WORK HISTORY

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

DW Green Co. | Tempe, AZ | 2009 - present

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Vertis | Phoenix, AZ | 2004 - 2009

EMAIL
lesleydreyer@hotmail.com





PORTFOLIO

https://lesleydreyer.github.io/portfolio

SKILLS

FRONT END:

- JavaScript- React- jQuery- Redux- Sass/SCSS- CSS- Bootstrap

BACK END:

- Express - MongoDB - Node.js - SQL

TESTING:

- Mocha - Enzyme - Chai - Jest - TravisCl

OTHER:

- GIT & Github - Heroku
- Gulp - Microsoft
- Adobe CS: Office: Word,
InDesign, Excel &
Photoshop - AND MORE!

EDUCATION

MENTORSHIP 2018-2019

Hadn't coded in awhile so I hired a mentor from Thinkful to teach me industry best practices.

ASSOCIATE IN SCIENCE COMPUTER PROGRAMMING

Mesa Community College, Arizona, 2009-2013

BACHELOR IN SCIENCE IN INDUSTRIAL TECHNOLOGY

Arizona State University, 1999-2003, Cum Laude, Graphic Information Technology specialization

Started as a production artist and worked up to a senior designer. Duties at both companies: design print ads, e-blasts, signage, brochures, and more in a fast-paced environment, communicate with clients and printers, proofread, work individually and on a team to prioritize workload, delegate work to production artists and provide tips and instruction to help ensure the ads are consistent and conform to brand standards.